Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
On orders from the Wizard King, Asta and his fellow black bulls headed for the seaside village of Rockway and the underwater temple that lay off its coast.
Their mission? To enter the well-guarded temple, secure its magic stone, and prevent the Eye of the Midnight Sun from fulfilling their ambition to topple the Clover Kingdom and establish a sovereign state.
However...
What are you messing around for?
But you're not.
Oh, hi, Captain Yomi.
Okay, you incompetent knuckleheads, listen up.
Apparently the underwater temple is beneath the surface of the ocean around here.
Unfortunately, the mana-driven currents are too strong, so even a skilled mage can't normally get near it.
The only time the mana is weak enough to even possibly access it is during a full moon.
If you didn't guess already, the underwater temple is on the ocean floor. You need magic to get there.
So, Noelle, that's where your water magic comes in. We're gonna hitch a ride on it.
But, sir, I'd need exceptional control over my magic to manage something like that. No, I can't do it!
You have to, Noelle. The full moon's a week away. You've got till then to learn to control your magic. Push past your limits.
Why are you keeping it so low in the dark?
How did your mind hold on it? There was no more.
Why are you keeping it so low?
How will you keep the sun out?
By the way you have to move forward.
You can't do this back, everybody get down
Can't do this back, hey, step back, step back
Whoa
運命の凍らみ I'm falling down
君と奏ってハーモニー 生まれ過去に置き去りのまま
君の強気の香りは まる心に引きずったまま
待ってるだけじゃもう足りない
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Get through with me
まっかり抱きしめ
明日のスルエイ
Get through with me
光灯して
真っ暗な明日
Get through with me
La la la la la la la la
La la la la la la
Get through with me
La la la la la la la la
目ど前の希望をつかまって
Listen, where do you think you're going?
Oh nowhere!
I just thought the place could use a little airing out is all.
Of course, sir.
Though, your foot?
Well, whadda you know?
How did that get there?
Feet.
They never listen.
You were about to abandon your work and go goof off.
Me? But I would never do something so irresponsible. Just taking a quick magic stroll.
This is not the time for your shenanigans. Now will you please do your work, sir? And close that window.
Fine.
Really, all the trouble the Eye of the Midnight Sun has been giving us lately, and you still insist on slacking off.
If you keep getting worked up like that, you're going to send yourself to an early grave.
And I'll have you to thank!
Speaking of the Midnight Sun, I wonder how Yami and his crew are coming along.
I only hope they've gotten down to business.
The Underwater Temple. I wish I could have gone.
Please, tell me more, sweetheart.
You are the light of my life, then, Raul.
Why, thank you, my dear.
Dammit, I told you to stay away from my fraud!
Sorry!
I wrote my name on it and everything!
Yeah, but food that's not yours just tastes better, you know?
My fraud!
Sweet dreams, my beautiful little angel!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Need more!
Jackasses, quit screwing around!
We're not on vacation, you know?
Now sit down and shut up.
I'm trying to concentrate here.
Sorry, Captain Yami!
Ah, doada estela, aveu muu
Ah, doada estela, aveu muu, uh-uh-la
Tsurume-heru, noe-ha-ta-te
Tsurume-heru, noe-ha-ta
Tsurume-heru, noe-net-viii-meu
Tsurume-heru, noe-fourie-no-amo
What a beautiful voice.
Almost like something out of a dream.
Is she from Rockoy?
Are these magical bubbles?
Is that the spirit of the sea?
Were you listening?
Oh my gosh!
Not what I was expecting.
Well, nothing I can do about it.
Wanna be friends?
Do-do-do-do-do-do.
She wants to be friends?
All right, I guess I should introduce myself.
I'm Kahono, and you?
My name's Noel, and this guy is Dorksta the Musclehead.
That's not my name, and I'm not a musclehead!
Huh, Noel and Dorksta the Musclehead.
You have such strange names.
Wait, you believe her?
Aw, come on!
Huh?
She's obviously making fun of me.
My real name's actually Asta.
Okay, it's nice to meet you, Asta.
So, Kahono, what are you doing out here so late?
Just singing.
Yeah, I gathered that much.
This is the perfect place for voice training.
The atmosphere, the acoustics, I just love singing here!
Voice training?
That's right!
You see, I have this dream.
Between my singing, dancing, and spellcasting...
I'm gonna become an idol!
Uh, what's an idol?
What?
You're joking, right?
No, sorry.
But they're all the rage in the common and noble realms.
Come on, you know idols!
Uh...
Okay, so idols are people who are so good at singing, dancing, and using magic that everyone everywhere knows who they are.
Well, except you, I guess.
Huh?
I'm gonna work and work and work and work until I make it as big as an idol and get crazy rich!
That's the reason you're doing it?
I don't see what's so great about money.
I mean, it just gets in the way.
You're wrong there.
You royals are basically rolling in the stuff, so you probably can't understand this.
But money?
It's a big deal.
I mean, without it, you can't buy pot potatoes.
If you don't have any pot potatoes, just eat steak instead.
Royalty!
There, you see?
Money is totally important.
Wow, dorksta, I feel like you really get me.
Please don't use that dumb nickname.
Sorry, dorksta.
Seriously, it's hasta.
Okay, right.
Sorry, I...
Hold on.
What's wrong?
Hmm?
Your body seems to be weakened, dorksta.
I told you it's...
Wait.
Huh?
Your muscles are holding on to a lot of fatigue.
They are?
You're sore when you move, right?
Yeah, but how could you tell?
Because it's my gift.
Your gift?
Here, I'll make it better.
Song recovery magic.
Healing lullaby.
So cool!
She's good.
It takes an incredibly delicate touch to direct magic with that much accuracy.
Well, how do you feel?
I don't know.
Oh!
Whoa!
That's awesome!
I was sore all over and now I don't hurt anywhere!
My body feels so light!
Bye-bye muscle fatigue!
Whatever you did really worked!
You're amazing, Kahano!
It's like I have a whole new body!
I've never seen someone use song recovery magic before.
That's great!
I'm glad it worked out.
Okay, that'll be a hundred yule, please.
You're charging me?
Just kidding.
Oh, good.
But not really!
Are you serious?
Money's a big deal, you know.
Take it.
Great, thanks!
And if you ever need another healing lullaby, I'm more than happy to help.
I can't believe I just lost a hundred yule.
Please, that's nothing.
Nothing?
That much money went by ten pot potatoes!
Like I said, nothing.
Royalty!
You two are so funny.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
Me too.
Wow, both of you?
That's crazy!
So am I!
Oh, really?
Well, now we definitely have to be friends.
Sure, sounds great.
You're pretty funny, too.
A friend who's a girl my own age?
That's new.
Fine!
If you insist, I suppose that would be acceptable.
I mean, I won't not be your friend.
Sorry, I guess I got a little carried away.
Little!
Wow, that's so cool!
The magic knights are amazing!
It's not a big deal.
It stands to reason that I would be one.
I am royalty.
I'm a commoner, though.
Okay, so what brings you here?
Vacation?
Nah, actually, we've got an important mission at the Underwater Temple.
Shut up, Asta!
The Underwater Temple?
Please don't listen to him.
It's top secret, so...
Okay, whatever.
So you two were out here pretty late.
Were you...
Well, you know...
What are you talking about?
As if we would ever!
The moonlight is so terribly romantic, though.
And the sound of the waves is perfect mood music.
Oh, I'm telling you, whatever you may have been thinking, it isn't like that at all, okay?
I'm out here training!
Like with magic?
Yes, with magic.
And I have a lot of work to do.
I can't go into detail, but I need to find a way to control my magic in a week before the full moon.
If I don't, then our mission will fail.
Right, I get the gist.
Let's see.
A control issue.
Very interesting.
Well, go on, Noelle.
Show me what you can do.
Huh?
Come on, Noelle!
You can do it!
Wow, she's really powerful!
Yes, I see. Nice job, Noelle!
Now, as your new friend, I have a little piece of advice for you.
I think you might be having trouble with control because you're trying too hard to hold back your mana.
Stand still and listen a sec.
Hear them?
I relax by listening to the sound of the waves,
and then try to cast my spells without letting myself get too caught up in my own thoughts and feelings.
Just like that?
I'm not a philosopher or anything,
but I've always thought that the best way to focus was to have a serene mind and a peaceful heart.
A serene mind?
I'm not sure I understand.
I do?
I always feel like I do my best fighting when my mind's clear and I'm not thinking about anything!
Oh, yeah, what would you know about it?
You don't even use magic and you're always not thinking.
Try to focus on your fondest memory.
Something comforting, you know?
Um, okay.
I'll try.
It's not that hard.
What about your family?
My family, huh?
The last thing the Steel Warrior Princess left behind was a useless little girl.
As if this tragedy were great enough already.
I don't see how anyone could ever accept a failure like you as their sister.
I swear, I'm trying, brother.
How is it possible you were born to the same mother as us?
Pathetic wretch.
You don't belong in our house.
Please, Nebra.
I do.
Nozel, will you just talk to me?
Why wasn't it you who died instead of our mother?
You're a mistake and an embarrassment to the Great Silva name.
You killed our mother.
I appreciate the advice, Kahono.
I'll keep practicing.
Just let me know if you get too tired.
I heal royals such as yourself for the low, low price of a hundred...
I mean, a thousand yule.
What's my fondest memory?
That's easy.
Sister Lily.
I don't know what's more blinding, the sun or your beauty.
Seriously?
You got it!
Yeah!
Go, Noelle!
Immortalized in sand.
I miss you, my little goddess.
Big sculpture.
Think maybe it's for a contest or something?
I'm not done.
Thank you, I needed that.
Sure, we can settle your tap later.
All right.
Not yet.
No, really.
I couldn't drink another drop.
Not yet!
Oh, yeah!
The full moon's tomorrow.
Noelle, this is it.
Tonight's my last chance.
Hey, Noelle!
Don't give up!
You can do this!
I'm running out of time, and I still have no semblance of control.
At this rate, our mission...
I just had a great idea!
You did?
Listen!
Stop thinking about control so much and just let your magic run wild!
Huh?
I've been thinking about something!
That thing you did the first time your magic went crazy might be exactly what we need!
It's like Kahano said before, right?
You're trying too hard to hold the mana back.
If you relax and let it do its thing, maybe the spell will actually work!
No!
That's just insane!
If it doesn't work, then...
It's fine!
I'll use my sword to keep everyone safe!
So quit worrying and go for it!
All right, but if this goes wrong, you better not come crying to me!
Okay.
I'm letting it go!
That's incredible!
I knew it!
This isn't working at all!
I'm nowhere close to having a serene mind!
Noelle!
Come on!
What the...
I guess it's true.
I really am hopeless.
A failure.
How am I supposed to focus on a fond memory when I don't have any?
Noelle!
What the hell are you doing up there, little Miss Royalty?
Is that really the best a Black Bull Knight can do?
Huh?
You're wasting all that super strong magic power of yours.
The sooner you can control it, the sooner we can spar together.
It's not like you'll die if you mess up, so just relax and next time have a little drink to sell your nerves.
You've got to be hungry after all that work, so hurry up and finish before I eat everything myself!
Don't worry.
If you fall, I'll be waiting right here to catch you.
Fall and I'll kick you right back up.
So make it work.
Just give it your all!
You can do it!
I know you can, Noelle!
Noelle, noelle, we're done!
He's a good job!
I was wrong.
I do have fond memories.
Hmm, so you're Noelle's little sister, huh?
Your brother was talking about you.
Apparently, you're a total failure who can't even control her magic.
You said you'd never pass the entrance exam, even if you tried.
You know, I've never seen a royal failure before.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
If you really want to fight, you could always join us.
That's right.
The worst of the worst Magic Knight squads, the Black Bulls, where all the best failures hang out.
I think you'll fit right in.
I spent so many years with my family, and I don't have a single good memory to show for it.
I've only been with the Black Bulls for a few months, and yet...
I have all these memories.
And most of them are good ones.
Very good ones.
The Black Bulls accepted me.
They relied on me.
And now, I want to do something for them!
Water creation magic!
See Dragon's Kratos!
It... it... worked!
We never doubted you, right now!
See Dragon's Cradle!
A new spell!
I did it!
I really did it!
What are you stopping now for?
Don't worry!
I'll keep the food dry!
Actually, it feels great when your cheeks are all flushed.
Phew!
Right!
That's my cue!
I'm coming to it!
That was my job!
No fair!
What are you doing, Dorksta?
I knew you could pull it off.
You spilled the hands off of me!
Why are there sheep?
Everything turned out perfectly, and I'd say that calls for a drink!
Oh, Kahuno!
That was awesome!
Did you see?
Huh?
Where'd she go?
All right!
It's party time!
Oh, yeah!
Let's light it up!
Yeah!
I told you to push past your limits, and that's exactly what you did.
I guess we better get going soon.
The temple's waiting for us.
You've got great friends.
In the end, they're the ones who should be here cheering you on.
I'm glad it all worked out.
Can't wait till the next time we meet, Noelle.
I'll see you in the temple!
Bye!
moi
my
Song recovery magic? That's amazing! Will you sing for me, please?
I'd be happy to! For 10 billion Yule!
Here!
Alright, let's go!
L-O-B-E!
What is it doing?
I meet some new friends! Once Noelle can control her magic, she'll be unstoppable!
I can't wait to see her again!
Black Clover, page 42, The Underwater Temple. My magic is song magic!